articlesphere.com 2016-03-05

# ArticleSphere.com Privacy Policies

| 

**Main Article Categories**

Alternative Medicine  
 Arts And Entertainment  
 Automotives  
 Beauty  
 Business  
 Communications  
 Computer And Technology  
 Disease And Illness   
 Finance  
 Food And Beverage  
 Health And Fitness  
 Home And Family  
 Home Based Business   
 Insurance  
 Internet And E-Business  
 Legal  
 News And Society  
 Pets And Animals  
 Product Reviews  
 Real Estate  
 Recreation And Sports   
 Reference And Education  
 Self Improvement  
 Shopping  
 Travel And Leisure   
 Women Health And Fitness  
 Women Interests And Issues  
 Work At Home  
 Writing And Speaking  
 All Categories  

|   | 

ArticleSphere.com Privacy Policy

ArticleSphere.com created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.articlesphere.com/contacts.php). 

At www.articlesphere.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.articlesphere.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.articlesphere.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.articlesphere.com does not use cookies. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.articlesphere.com.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.articlesphere.com and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include...  
Google Adsense  
Chitika  
Infolinks 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.articlesphere.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.articlesphere.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.articlesphere.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

|   | 

**Writers/Authors**

Author Terms of Service  
Sign Up Free Account  
Submission Guidelines  
Login to Submit Articles  

**Publishers**

Publisher Terms of Service  
Syndicate Category Articles  
Subscribe Category Articles  

**News Room**

Press Release Oct 20th 2005: New Article Search Engine Directory Solves Website Traffic Generation Problems

**Useful Resources**

[Free Trade Magazine Subscriptions & Technical Document Downloads](http://articlesphere.tradepub.com/)  

---|---|---|---|---  

**United States of America, USA [Alabama, Alaska, Arizona, Arkansas, California, Colorado, Connecticut, Delaware, Florida, Georgia, Hawaii, Idaho, Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, Kansas, Kentucky, Louisiana, Maine, Maryland, Massachusetts, Michigan, Minnesota, Mississippi, Missouri, Montana, Nebraska, Nevada, New Hampshire, New Jersey, New Mexico, New York, North Carolina, North Dakota, Ohio, Oklahoma, Oregon, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, South Carolina, South Dakota, Tennessee, Texas, Utah, Vermont, Virginia, Washington, West Virginia, Wisconsin, Wyoming]** . **United Kingdom, UK** **[ England (Avon, Bedfordshire, Berkshire, Bristol, Buckinghamshire, Cambridgeshire, Cheshire, Cleveland, Cornwall, Cumberland, Cumbria, Derbyshire, Devon, Dorset, Durham, East Suffolk, East Sussex, Essex, Gloucestershire, Greater Manchester, Hampshire, Hereford and Worcester, Herefordshire, Hertfordshire, Humberside, Huntingdon and Peterborough, Huntingdonshire, Isle of Ely, Isle of Wight, Kent, Lancashire, Leicestershire, Lincolnshire, London, Merseyside, Middlesex, Norfolk, Northamptonshire, Northumberland, North Humberside, North Yorkshire, Nottinghamshire, Oxfordshire, Soke of Peterborough, Rutland, Shropshire, Somerset, South Humberside, South Yorkshire, Staffordshire, Suffolk, Surrey, Sussex, Tyne and Wear, Warwickshire, West Midlands, West Suffolk, West Sussex, West Yorkshire, Wiltshire, Worcestershire, Yorkshire,)**, **Scotland (Aberdeen, Aberdeenshire, Angus, Argyll, Ayrshire, Banffshire, Berwickshire, Bute, Caithness, Clackmannanshire, Cromartyshire, Dumfriesshire, Dunbartonshire, Dundee, East Lothian, Edinburgh, Fife, Glasgow, Inverness-shire, Kincardineshire, Kinross-shire, Kirkcudbrightshire, Lanarkshire, Midlothian, Moray, Naimshire, Orkney, Peeblesshire, Perthshire, Renfrewshire, Ross and Cromarty, Ross-shire, Roxburghshire, Selkirkshire, Shetland, Stirlingshire, Sutherland, West Lothian, Wigtownshire)**, **Wales (Anglesey, Brecknockshire, Caemarfonshire, Cardiganshire, Carmarthenshire, Clwyd, Denbighshire, Dyfed, Flintshire, Glamorgan, Gwent, Gwynedd, Merionethshire, Mid Glamorgan, Monmouthshire, Montgomeryshire, Pembrokeshire, Powys, Radnorshire, South Glamorgan, West Glamorgan)**, **Northern Ireland (Antrim, Armagh, Belfast, Down, Fermanagh, Londonderry, Tyrone)]** . **Canada [Alberta, British Columbia, Manitoba, New Brunswick, Newfoundland and Labrador, Nova Scotia, Ontario, Prince Edward Island, Quebec, Saskatchewan, Northwest Territories, Nunavut, Yukon]** . **Australia [Ashmore and Cartier Islands, Australian Antarctic Territory, Australian Capital Territory, Christmas Island, Cocos (Keeling) Islands, Coral Sea Islands, Heard Island and McDonald Islands, Jervis Bay Territory, New South Wales, Norfolk Island, Northern Territory, Queensland, South Australia, Tasmania, Victoria, Western Australia] ** . **Norway [ostfold, Akershus, Oslo, Hedmark, Oppland, Buskerud, Vestfold, Telemark, Aust-Agder, Vest-Agder, Rogaland, Hordaland, Svalbard, Sogn og Fjordane, More og Romsdal, Sor-Trondelag, Nord-Trondelag, Nordland, Troms, Finnmark]** . Afghanistan . Albania . Algeria . American Samoa . Andorra . Angola . Anguilla . Antarctica . Antigua & Barbuda . Argentina . Armenia . Aruba . Austria . Azerbaijan . Bahamas . Bahrain . Bangladesh . Barbados . Belarus . Belgium . Belize . Benin . Bermuda . Bhutan . Bolivia . Bonaire . Bosnia-Herzegovina . Botswana . Brazil . British Virgin Islands . Brunei Darrusalam . Bulgaria . Burkina Faso . Burundi . Cambodia . Cameroon . Cape Verde . Cayman Islands . Central African Republic . Chad . Channel Islands . Chile . China . Christmas Island . Colombia . Comoros . Congo . Congo (Dem. Rep.) . Cook Islands . Costa Rica . Cote d'Ivoire . Croatia . Cuba . Curacao . Cyprus . Czech Republic . Denmark . Djibouti . Dominica . Dominican Republic . East Timor . Ecuador . Egypt . El Salvador . Equatorial Guinea . Eritrea . Estonia . Ethiopia . Falkland Islands and Dependencies . Faroe Islands . Fiji . Finland . France . French Guiana . French Polynesia . Gabon . Gambia . Gaza . Georgia . Germany . Ghana . Gibraltar . Greece . Greenland . Grenada . Guadeloupe . Guam . Guatemala . Guinea . Guinea-Bissau . Guyana . Haiti . Hawaiian Islands . Honduras . Hong Kong . Hungary . Iceland . India . Indonesia . Iran . Iraq . Isle Of Man . Israel . Italy . Ivory Coast . Jamaica . Japan . Johnston Atoll . Jordan . Kazakhstan . Kenya . Kiribati . Korea (North) . Korea (South) . Kuwait . Kyrgyzstan . Laos . Latvia . Lebanon . Leeward Islands . Lesotho . Liberia . Libya . Liechtenstein . Lithuania . Luxembourg . Macau . Macedonia . Madagascar . Malawi . Malaysia . Maldives . Mali . Malta . Marshall Islands . Martinique . Mauritania . Mauritius . Mexico . Micronesia (Federated States) . Midway Islands . Moldova . Monaco . Mongolia . Montserrat . Morocco . Mosquito Coast . Mozambique . Myanmar (Burma) . Namibia . Nauru . Navassa Island . Nepal . Netherlands . Netherlands Antilles . New Caledonia . New Zealand . Nicaragua . Niger . Nigeria . Niue . Norfolk Island . Northern Mariana Islands . Oman . Pakistan . Palau . Palestine . Panama . Papua New Guinea . Paracel Islands . Paraguay . Peru . Philippines . Pitcairn Islands . Poland . Portugal . Puerto Rico . Qatar . Reunion . Romania . Russia . Rwanda . Ryukyu Islands . Saint Helena . Saint Kitts and Nevis . Saint Lucia . Saint Pierre & Miquelon . Saint Vincent & The Grenadines . Samoa . San Marino . Sao Tome & Principe . Saudi Arabia . Senegal . Serbia . Seychelles . Sierra Leone . Singapore . Slovakia . Slovenia . Solomon Islands . Somalia . South Africa . Spain . Sri Lanka . Sudan . Suriname . Swaziland . Sweden . Switzerland . Syria . Taiwan . Tajikistan . Tanzania . Thailand . Togo . Tonga . Transkei . Trinidad & Tobago . Tunisia . Turkey . Turkmenistan . Turks and Caicos Islands . Tuvalu . US Virgin Islands . Uganda . Ukraine . United Arab Emirates . Upper Volta . Uruguay . Uzbekistan . Vanuatu . Vatican City (Holy See) . Venezuela . Vietnam . Wake Island . Windward Islands . Yemen . Yugoslavia . Zaire . Zambia . Zimbabwe
